deep Tech is today important for the
world deep Tech is important to save the
planet deep Tech is important to ensure
that our future is what we want our
future to be this program that the
government of India funds to create uh
SE for companies for the
government
how do we look to consume insurance with
technology so uh do uh read the report
it'll be up on uh both our websites and
it's a
[Music]
free it's a very important topic um very
timely um you know Innovation is at the
Forefront for all major organizations
whether you know you look at Global
organizations organizations in Fortune
500 2,000 and so on so it was really
great to partner with
[Music]
nascom